(horn honking)
(crowd cheering)
(upbeat country music)
♪ You can tell the world
you never was my girl ♪
♪ You can burn my clothes
up when I'm gone ♪
♪ Or you can tell your friends
just what a fool I've been ♪
♪ And laugh and joke
about me on the phone ♪
♪ You can tell my arms
go back to the farm ♪
♪ You can tell my feet
to hit the floor ♪
♪ Or you can tell my lips
to tell my fingertips ♪
♪ They won't be reaching
out for you no more ♪
♪ But don't tell my heart,
my achy breaky heart ♪
♪ I just don't think
he'd understand ♪
♪ And if you tell my heart,
my achy breaky heart ♪
♪ He might blow up
and kill this man ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪♪♪
♪ You can tell your ma
I moved to Arkansas ♪
♪ Or you can tell your
dog to bite my leg ♪
♪ Or tell your brother Cliff,
whose fist can tell my lip ♪
♪ He never really
liked me anyway ♪
♪ Or tell your Aunt Louise,
tell anything you please ♪
♪ Myself already
knows I'm not okay ♪
♪ Or you can tell my eyes
to watch out for my mind ♪
♪ It might be walking
out on me today ♪
♪ But don't tell my heart,
my achy breaky heart ♪
♪ I just don't think
he'd understand ♪
♪ And if you tell my heart,
my achy breaky heart ♪
♪ He might blow up
and kill this man ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Don't tell my heart,
my achy breaky heart ♪
♪ I just don't think
he'd understand ♪
♪ And if you tell my heart,
my achy breaky heart ♪
♪ He might blow up
and kill this man ♪
♪ Don't tell my heart,
my achy breaky heart ♪
♪ I just don't think
he'd understand ♪
♪ And if you tell my heart,
my achy breaky heart ♪
♪ He might blow up
and kill this man ♪
♪ Ooh ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Woo ♪
(crowd cheering)